[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "What was it like for you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "It was an unbelievable day.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "an", "unbelievable", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "I mean, Commissioner, did you get a sense of your men, that these brave firemen feeling any sense of closure or is it not really that kind of emotion?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "Commissioner", ",", "did", "you", "get", "a", "sense", "of", "your", "men", ",", "that", "these", "brave", "firemen", "feeling", "any", "sense", "of", "closure", "or", "is", "it", "not", "really", "that", "kind", "of", "emotion", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "WDT", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "Well, I don't like to use the word closure.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "like", "to", "use", "the", "word", "closure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Yes, I mean, do you think New York firemen would like to see a picture of a dead Osama bin Laden?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "do", "you", "think", "New", "York", "firemen", "would", "like", "to", "see", "a", "picture", "of", "a", "dead", "Osama", "bin", "Laden", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "I spoke to many firefighters today, and they all feel like I feel, that we go along with the decision of the president.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "spoke", "to", "many", "firefighters", "today", ",", "and", "they", "all", "feel", "like", "I", "feel", ",", "that", "we", "go", "along", "with", "the", "decision", "of", "the", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York", "Osama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 57, "question": "When you hear that, what is your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "hear", "that", ",", "what", "is", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 58, "answer": "It doesn't surprise me one bit, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "n't", "surprise", "me", "one", "bit", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RBR", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "Were you pleased when you heard that bin Laden had been killed?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "pleased", "when", "you", "heard", "that", "bin", "Laden", "had", "been", "killed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "I'm pleased that he will no longer be around to do any harm to anybody.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "pleased", "that", "he", "will", "no", "longer", "be", "around", "to", "do", "any", "harm", "to", "anybody", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "What did you think of the decision not to publish the images of a dead bin Laden?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "think", "of", "the", "decision", "not", "to", "publish", "the", "images", "of", "a", "dead", "bin", "Laden", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Well, personally, I don't need to see that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "personally", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "need", "to", "see", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 130, "question": "Why would you simply believe what they tell you on this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "would", "you", "simply", "believe", "what", "they", "tell", "you", "on", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 131, "answer": "I'm vociferous in my skepticism of those who don't tell the truth and who have a track record of not telling the truth.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "vociferous", "in", "my", "skepticism", "of", "those", "who", "do", "n't", "tell", "the", "truth", "and", "who", "have", "a", "track", "record", "of", "not", "telling", "the", "truth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "I mean, when he said, before he was elected, that he would close down Guantanamo Bay, and then he doesn't do that, I mean, that's not entirely being straight with you, is it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "when", "he", "said", ",", "before", "he", "was", "elected", ",", "that", "he", "would", "close", "down", "Guantanamo", "Bay", ",", "and", "then", "he", "does", "n't", "do", "that", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "that", "'s", "not", "entirely", "being", "straight", "with", "you", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "Well, he hasn't done it yet.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "has", "n't", "done", "it", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Guantanamo Bay"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "WP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "But if he was executed, is that lawful or would you have preferred him to have been captured alive and brought back to trial maybe in New York?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "he", "was", "executed", ",", "is", "that", "lawful", "or", "would", "you", "have", "preferred", "him", "to", "have", "been", "captured", "alive", "and", "brought", "back", "to", "trial", "maybe", "in", "New", "York", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "Well, I just -- I think that -- and I don't think I'm the only one who feels this way.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "just", "--", "I", "think", "that", "--", "and", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "I", "'m", "the", "only", "one", "who", "feels", "this", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "What do you think about the fact that bin Laden appears to have been there for up to five years, in this large property right next to Pakistanis' military intelligence?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "about", "the", "fact", "that", "bin", "Laden", "appears", "to", "have", "been", "there", "for", "up", "to", "five", "years", ",", "in", "this", "large", "property", "right", "next", "to", "Pakistanis", "'", "military", "intelligence", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "EX", "IN", "NN", "TO", "CD", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "OORE: Right next door to it.", "answer_tokens": ["OORE", ":", "Right", "next", "door", "to", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Would you go further and say that President Obama or his intelligence advisers -- are you suggesting that any of them had knowledge for a considerable period of time?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "go", "further", "and", "say", "that", "President", "Obama", "or", "his", "intelligence", "advisers", "--", "are", "you", "suggesting", "that", "any", "of", "them", "had", "knowledge", "for", "a", "considerable", "period", "of", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "I would like to know that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "like", "to", "know", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 324, "question": "Where?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Would you know --", "answer_tokens": ["Would", "you", "know", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 326, "question": "Well, you don't believe al Qaeda exists in any form?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "do", "n't", "believe", "al", "Qaeda", "exists", "in", "any", "form", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 327, "answer": "I think there are a lot of people running around calling themselves al Qaeda.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "are", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "running", "around", "calling", "themselves", "al", "Qaeda", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tunisia"]}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "Do you believe al Qaeda has been dismantled?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "al", "Qaeda", "has", "been", "dismantled", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Well, I think, listen, actually, the day that al Qaeda was dismantled, personally, frankly, what I think, it was the day that the revolution began in Tunisia.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", ",", "listen", ",", "actually", ",", "the", "day", "that", "al", "Qaeda", "was", "dismantled", ",", "personally", ",", "frankly", ",", "what", "I", "think", ",", "it", "was", "the", "day", "that", "the", "revolution", "began", "in", "Tunisia", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "Are you slightly more critical there?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "slightly", "more", "critical", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "JJR", "JJ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Well, first of all, he inherited a huge mess.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "he", "inherited", "a", "huge", "mess", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 383, "question": "Not one?", "question_tokens": ["Not", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 384, "answer": "Not one.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "one", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald Trump", "Obama"]}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", ":", "RB", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "But when you see the Donald Trump Birther issue dominating the news agenda, and there was a real prospect of perhaps Donald Trump running for president, what was your reaction to that?", "question_tokens": ["But", "when", "you", "see", "the", "Donald", "Trump", "Birther", "issue", "dominating", "the", "news", "agenda", ",", "and", "there", "was", "a", "real", "prospect", "of", "perhaps", "Donald", "Trump", "running", "for", "president", ",", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "I hope in this coming election year that people remember that -- not just Donald Trump, but a majority of the people who called themselves Republicans said that they didn't believe or they weren't sure that President Obama was an American.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "hope", "in", "this", "coming", "election", "year", "that", "people", "remember", "that", "--", "not", "just", "Donald", "Trump", ",", "but", "a", "majority", "of", "the", "people", "who", "called", "themselves", "Republicans", "said", "that", "they", "did", "n't", "believe", "or", "they", "were", "n't", "sure", "that", "President", "Obama", "was", "an", "American", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Donald Trump Birther"], "PERSON": ["Donald Trump"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "But when he was coming out with stuff about China and OPEC and so on, I actually found myself nodding in agreement, that America has been pretty weak in relation to OPEC and China, hasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "when", "he", "was", "coming", "out", "with", "stuff", "about", "China", "and", "OPEC", "and", "so", "on", ",", "I", "actually", "found", "myself", "nodding", "in", "agreement", ",", "that", "America", "has", "been", "pretty", "weak", "in", "relation", "to", "OPEC", "and", "China", ",", "has", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Well, that's a much larger issue than the way that he was just kind of simplifying it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "much", "larger", "issue", "than", "the", "way", "that", "he", "was", "just", "kind", "of", "simplifying", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["OPEC", "OPEC"], "LOCATION": ["China", "America", "China"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "PDT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "What is the next cage that you're going to rattle?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "next", "cage", "that", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "rattle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Well, I don't talk to my next project while I'm doing it for all the obvious reasons.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "talk", "to", "my", "next", "project", "while", "I", "'m", "doing", "it", "for", "all", "the", "obvious", "reasons", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Is that correct?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "correct", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "I'm afraid it was a beauty and the beast situation, so the beast has to leave the stage.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "afraid", "it", "was", "a", "beauty", "and", "the", "beast", "situation", ",", "so", "the", "beast", "has", "to", "leave", "the", "stage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]